[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '色んな' read in word?",
        "answer": "Різноманітний"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '旅' read in word?",
        "answer": "Подорож"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '葉っぱ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Листочок"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji '生け花' read in word?",
        "answer": "Ікебана (мистецтво квітів)"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '焼き芋' read in word?",
        "answer": "Смажений батат"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '用事' read in word?",
        "answer": "Справи"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '宿題' read in word?",
        "answer": "Д,З"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '大変' read in word?",
        "answer": "Жахіття"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji 'バス停' read in word?",
        "answer": "Автобусна зупинка"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '門番' read in word?",
        "answer": "Охоронець, вахта"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the kanji '並びます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Стояти у ряд"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the kanji '国立' read in word?",
        "answer": "Національний"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the kanji '例えば' read in word?",
        "answer": "Наприклад"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the kanji '授業' read in word?",
        "answer": "Урок"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the kanji '簡単(な）' read in word?",
        "answer": "Простий"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the kanji 'お菓子' read in word?",
        "answer": "Солодощі"
    }
]